<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sunny Wong</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/</link><description>Recent content on Sunny Wong</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Sunny Wong</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 02:46:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advanced Physics Lab 2 The Photoelectric Effect</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/photoelectric/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/photoelectric/</guid><description>Enter description here&amp;hellip; [Work in Progress]
##Note: I am currently having difficulty uploading images, but there will be 2-3 images for every project subcategory</description></item><item><title>Project 2 Understanding Room Temperature MoTe2</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/posts/mote2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/posts/mote2/</guid><description>#Introduction
To better understand the room temperature phase of the transition metal dichalcogenide MoTe2, we take cross sectional Scanning Transmission Electron Microscopy (STEM) images of the bulk material at both the many-layer and few-nanometer limit. With these STEM images, we can map the interlayer displacements using image processing techniques in python. Overall, the project is divided into several steps; 1. identify any common stacking displacements across the cross-sectional images, 2. simulate a robust library of plan-view STEM images using this data, and 3.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Physics Lab 1 Learning the Arduino Uno</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/ardunio/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/ardunio/</guid><description>Introduction Data acquisition, or the collection of real-world measurements and conversion into digital data, has many applications within daily life and research. When performing an experiment, it is essential to regulate laboratory conditions and helpful to automate the data collection process to reduce sources of error. To explore data acquisition, this project focuses on using the Arduino Uno to monitor temperature, manage an external fan and heating pad based on the temperature readings, and display data on to an LCD display.</description></item><item><title>Digital Signals and Image Processing Image Registration Project</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/imagereg/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/imagereg/</guid><description>#Introduction
Within medical image processing, the process of image registration remains essential for the automated analysis of medical images. By comparing a set of experimental medical images to an established set of templates, the experimental images can undergo semantic segmentation- or the process of dividing the image into a set of various regions with established labels. In this project, I explore the application of image registration and segmentation on the coronal sections of the brain- indexed from a larger set of test fMRI images.</description></item><item><title>Project 1 Stacking Faults in STEM images</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/posts/nb3br8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/posts/nb3br8/</guid><description>#Introduction
Going from high to low temperatures, Nb​3Br8​ crystals undergo a transition from a paramagnetic material to a nonmagnetic material and experience a shift within its stack of 2-D atomic layers (Pasco et al., 2019). With lower temperatures, Pasco et al.(2019) observes a transition from high to low magnetic susceptibility and structural rearrangement from a two-layer unit cell to a six-layer unit cell. However, the role of stacking faults, or the misalignment of atomic layers, in the magnetic transition remains unknown.</description></item><item><title>Contact me</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/about/</guid><description>Email: sw758@cornell.edu</description></item></channel></rss>