<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Researches on Sunny Wong</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/research/</link><description>Recent content in Researches on Sunny Wong</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Sunny Wong</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 02:46:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Project 2 Understanding Room Temperature MoTe2</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/research/mote2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/research/mote2/</guid><description>Introduction To better understand the room temperature phase of the transition metal dichalcogenide MoTe2, we take cross sectional Scanning Transmission Electron Microscopy (STEM) images of the bulk material at both the many-layer and few-nanometer limit. With these STEM images, we can map the interlayer displacements using image processing techniques in python. Overall, the project is divided into several steps: 1. identify any common stacking displacements across the cross-sectional images, 2. simulate a robust library of plan-view STEM images using this data, and 3.</description></item><item><title>Project 1 Stacking Faults in Nb3Br8</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/research/nb3br8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/research/nb3br8/</guid><description>Introduction Going from high to low temperatures, Nb​3Br8​ crystals undergo a transition from a paramagnetic material to a nonmagnetic material and experience a shift within its stack of 2-D atomic layers (Pasco et al., 2019). With lower temperatures, Pasco et al.(2019) observes a transition from high to low magnetic susceptibility and structural rearrangement from a two-layer unit cell to a six-layer unit cell. However, the role of stacking faults, or the misalignment of atomic layers, in the magnetic transition remains unknown.</description></item></channel></rss>