<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Works on Sunny Wong</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/</link><description>Recent content in Works on Sunny Wong</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Sunny Wong</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 02:46:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advanced Physics Lab 2 The Photoelectric Effect</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/photoelectric/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/photoelectric/</guid><description>Enter description here&amp;hellip; [Work in Progress]
Note: I am currently having difficulty uploading images, but there will be 2-3 images for every project subcategory</description></item><item><title>Advanced Physics Lab 1 Learning the Arduino Uno</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/arduino/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/arduino/</guid><description>Introduction Data acquisition, or the collection of real-world measurements and conversion into digital data, has many applications within daily life and research. When performing an experiment, it is essential to regulate laboratory conditions and helpful to automate the data collection process to reduce sources of error. To explore data acquisition, this project focuses on using the Arduino Uno to monitor temperature, manage an external fan and heating pad based on the temperature readings, and display data on to an LCD display.</description></item><item><title>Digital Signals and Image Processing Image Registration Project</title><link>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/imagereg/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sunnyw1.github.io/draft/work/imagereg/</guid><description>Introduction Within medical image processing, the process of image registration remains essential for the automated analysis of medical images. By comparing a set of experimental medical images to an established set of templates, the experimental images can undergo semantic segmentation- or the process of dividing the image into a set of various regions with established labels. In this project, I explore the application of image registration and segmentation on the coronal sections of the brain- indexed from a larger set of test fMRI images.</description></item></channel></rss>